Conduciendo Fumado: Redux
Folder name: condfumadored
Release Date: 2023-03-05
Author: EstebanMz
	Contact info:
	Discord: EstebanMz#4398
	Mail: estebanmz@rva.lat
Original Author: Seth

Changelog:
- Reverse version available, with heavier rain, harder to drive terrain and lower lighting to simulate it being late at night.
- The base road, excluding ramps and obstacles, has been merged and edited on Blender into one piece, which now is the world file itself and not a bunch of instances.
- Properties added to the dirt road and the ramps, now the dirt road is bumpy, with lower grip and has smoke effects. It's recommended to not disable Particles effect on Video Settings.
- Bug fixes. Many, many bugs has been fixed.
- Special thanks to yun and WaluigiMB for their stubborness on this suggestion, and yun for the initial steps to make this Redux possible.
- Special thanks and credits to kiwi for his Rain Pack, as it was helpful in the development of this Redux (Available here: https://www.revoltworld.net/dl/rain-pack-for-track-makers/)

Additional Info:
- Original instance kit for the creation of the original track is made by JimK (Available here: http://revoltzone.net/instances/8912/JimK%20Offroad%20Arena%20Kit)
- The track originally came bundled with a copyrighted song, that one being "Satellite" by The Faulty. It wasn't taken out to respect the original creator.
- Custom properties values are free to use for your creations, is appreciated if you contact me beforehand.


// ORIGINAL DESCRIPTION //

..:::Conduciendo Fumado:::..

→→→Pista hecha por Seth ←←← ..:::2014:::..
=====================================================
Longitud: 524m
Tipo: Extrema
Nombre de la carpeta: cond_fumado
E-mail: seth.rv@hotmail.com
Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/seth.rv2015
=====================================================
Esta pista va dedicada para todos los vagos de Argentina que les gusta la marihuana :D

Le he agregado ♫♫-Musica-♫♫ para animar el ambiente de la pista espero que les guste ♪♪♪

Por ultimo les digo que voy a seguir haciendo pistas lo mejor que pueda para que ustedes puedan divertirse y entretenerse... 

Bueno a disfrutar!! 

=====================================================


